bluebottlecoffee.com 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy | Blue Bottle Coffee

## Privacy

Blue Bottle Coffee is committed to protecting your privacy. This Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website and our practices for using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.  

We may from time to time update this Policy, so we invite you to review this web page periodically. In the event this Policy changes, we will inform you by posting an updated Policy on this web page. All changes will go into effect on the date noted above. The new Policy will apply to all past and current users of our website and will replace any prior Policies.

### What Information We Collect and How We Use It

We do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. Visitors to our website are not required to register or provide information to us in order to view our website.

If you choose to establish a Blue Bottle Coffee account, we collect the following information about you: name, address, phone number, email address, username and password. We use the information you supply for the purpose of providing the services you have requested, and as described in this Policy. In addition, we may from time to time contact you via email or regular mail unless you opt-out by following the instructions in the "opting out" section of this Policy.

If you shop with us, we collect the following information about you: name, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, billing information including credit card numbers and expiration dates as well as the names, addresses and phone numbers of gift recipients (if any). We use your name, address, phone number and billing/credit card information to process your order or as otherwise described in this Policy.

The email address you provide is used for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your orders or as otherwise described in this Policy. We may also contact you occasionally via email or regular mail to keep you up-to-date on the latest Blue Bottle Coffee news. If you would like to opt out of receiving mailings from us, just let us know (see contact information below). Also, gift recipients may, from time to time, receive offers from us regarding new products and services that we think may be of interest to them. We allow gift recipients the option to opt out of receiving future marketing-related communications from us.

In certain instances, we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, Blue Bottle Coffee or others. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it. In the event of a merger, consolidation or sale or transfer of all or substantially all of our company or its assets, personal information collected by our website may be transferred to the purchaser or the new company.

### Use of Cookies

Our website uses "cookies." A cookie is a small file that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help us determine whether a visitor to our website has visited our website before or if he or she is a new visitor. Cookies also allow Blue Bottle Coffee account registrants to save time during checkout on return visits. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but they should also allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of cookies. Please note that if you disable cookies, certain aspects of our website will not function properly, such as the shopping cart. Our cookies do not track any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookies do not extract any information from your computer.

We may use third-party analytical tools to help us better understand how you use our website. These analytical tools will place cookies on your computer to collect information. The information collected by these analytical tools will tell us things like which search engine referred you to our website, how you navigated around our website and what you purchased. This information will help us to better serve you with more personalized information and product offerings. The third party provider of the analytical tools may only use your personal information to perform services for us and is contractually required to maintain all of the information it collects and analyzes for us securely and in confidence. This third party may not share your personal information with anyone else, or use it for any other purpose, except on an aggregate, non-identifiable basis.

### Updating, Deleting, Editing Your Account Information

After setting up an account with Blue Bottle Coffee, you can access, review, correct and/or delete all of the personally identifiable information you provided to us by logging into your account. You may also ask us to assist by emailing us at [support@bluebottlecoffee.com](mailto:support@bluebottlecoffee.com).

### Third Party Service Providers

We sometimes employ other companies and individuals to perform services for us. For example, we may hire agencies to help administer consumer promotions, to analyze data, to process and fulfill orders you place, and to provide customer service. We may share your personally identifiable information with these parties, who have agreed to hold this information in confidence, not to use it for any purpose except to carry out the requested service, and to honor Blue Bottle Coffee’s privacy and security policies in the way this information is handled.

### Security

We take your privacy and security seriously. For this reason, we maintain administrative, physical and technical safeguards that are designed to protect your personal information from accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, access, disclosure or use.

### Opting Out

If you would rather not receive marketing emails from us, please let us know by contacting us as indicated below.

### Contacting Us

You may ask questions, submit comments and opt out of receiving updates and other mailings from us by contacting us via email at [support@bluebottlecoffee.com](mailto:support@bluebottlecoffee.com), via phone at (510) 653-3394 or regular mail at Blue Bottle Coffee, Inc., 300 Webster Street, Oakland, CA 94607.

Last modified: March 30, 2016
